

CONTACT





duvano30496@hotmail.com



Bogotá, Colombia



https://github.com/Duvan HB?tab=repositories

SKILLS

HTML & CSS

TypeScript - JavaScript

C# .Net Core



SQL Server

Wordprees

LANGUAGES



Duván Hernández Barrios Software Engineer

Electronic engineer from the Francisco José de Caldas District University, experienced in web and mobile application development. Good knowledge in HTML, CSS and TypeScript, experience in Angular and Ionic frameworks for the frontend, knowledge of the Redux data handling pattern. Knowledge of C# with the .NET Core framework for the backend.

Management of relational databases with SQL server.

Solid knowledge in the JavaScript language. With innovation, conceptual thinking, initiative and results orientation.

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

October 2021- present

Bizagi

Creation of web and mobile applications for the frontend with Angular Creation of services or business logic in the backend with .Net core Database management with Sql Server Technologies used: TypeScript, HTML, CSS, Angular, .Net Core, Sql Server.

Angular development engineer

March 2021- present

Global Hitss

Creation of web and mobile applications for the frontend with Angular Technologies used: TypeScript, HTML, CSS, Angular.

Junior development engineer

February 2020- March 2021

Intergrupo

Development of applications with Angular for the frontend.

Business logic for the backend with .Net Core.

Database with Sql server.

Technologies used: TypeScript, HTML, CSS, Angular, .Net Core, Sql Server.

Internship

August 2019- February 2020

Intergrupo

Help creating web and mobile applications with the framework called Angular.

Technologies used: TypeScript, HTML, CSS, Angular.

EDUCATION

Electronic Engineer

January 2014- August 2020

Francisco José de Caldas District University

Bachelor

February 2002- December 2013

Alejandro Obregón High School

OTHER STUDIES

Course: Modern JavaScript 20 hours Course: HTML & CSS 40 hours Course: Angular from zero to expert 50 hours **Course: Git version control** 15 hours

Course: C#, .Net core 20 hours **Certification: Azure fundamental** Microsoft AZ-900

Certification: Programming in C# Microsoft 20-483